fplmaps.com 2013-06-07

# NextEra Energy, Inc. | Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

We would like to take this opportunity to thank you for visiting the NextEra Energy, Inc. (“NextEra Energy”) family of websites (the “NextEra Energy Sites”).

The family of NextEra Energy Sites includes: nexteraenergy.com, fpl.com, nexteraenergyresources.com, earthera.com, fplfibernet.com, fplcareers.com, and other sites where this Privacy Policy is found. NextEra Energy and its direct and indirect wholly-owned subsidiaries and its affiliates are collectively hereafter referred to herein as “NextEra Energy,” “we,” “us” or “our.”

By using any of the NextEra Energy Sites, you represent that you agree with our Privacy Policy and our _[Terms of Use](http://www.nexteraenergy.com/legal_notice.shtml)_. If you do not agree with any one of or both of the aforementioned, please do not use any of the NextEra Energy Sites.

## HOW WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of any personal information you provide on this website. We use secure socket layer technology to help keep the personal information you provide on this site secure.

Even though we maintain a secure website, we strongly encourage you to keep your user ID and password confidential. If for any reason whatsoever you feel your user ID and password have become compromised, please contact us immediately.

## HOW WE COLLECT AND USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND WHY WE COLLECT IT

If you choose to supply us with your personal information, we will only use such information consistent with our policies regarding the establishment of service accounts, our Terms of Use and as may be described in this Privacy Policy. In connection with our efforts to better serve you, we may also share your personal information with our subsidiaries and affiliates.

Please note that certain personal information must be supplied in order to establish a service account. We use this information to provide service to you and to invoice you for services provided. You may also be required to provide certain information when signing up for an account on our website.

We also collect certain other information when you visit any one of the NextEra Energy Sites. This other information tells us such things as how many users visit our site and which pages they have chosen to access. This information also assists us with maintaining and designing a user friendly website for you to enjoy. We collect this information through “cookie” technology as explained below. This other information includes:

  * click-stream data

  * HTTP protocol elements

  * search terms

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * completion and support of the current activity

  * website and system administration

  * research and development

To assist customers with technical problems, we may also collect local Web configuration information, including:

  * browser type

  * operating system

  * browser settings

In addition, our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer when you visit our website. This information may include the type of browser software you use, the operating system you’re running, the IP address assigned to your computer or Internet connection, and the IP address of the website, if any, that referred you to our website. Our technical staff may also use this information to assist customers with technical problems.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

## COOKIES

We use browser cookies to enhance your online experience and make your use of the NextEra Energy Sites more efficient. Browser cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. We utilize browser cookies to tell us, for example, whether you’ve visited any of our sites before, or if you’re a new visitor.

Browser cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. If you wish to stop receiving browser cookies from us, please visit the “help” portion of the tool bar to learn how to stop the installation of cookies. The tool bar can help direct you on how to be notified when you receive a new browser cookie, and how to disable existing browser cookies. Remember though, without browser cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features.

We may also use various other types of cookies on our website to enhance your online experience. Similar to browser cookies, such cookies can store more complex data.

Certain online service request forms are available to residential and business customers. These forms require the use of cookies to complete a secure connection with your computer. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use our online applications that require you to log in. Other information on the website, however, may still be accessed.

## CONFIDENTIALITY; EXCEPTIONS

We do not knowingly reveal any personal information that is provided by our customers through the NextEra Energy Sites to any third parties except as provided in this Privacy Policy, when requested to do so by a governmental agency having jurisdiction, by a court of competent jurisdiction or other operation of law, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. All information provided by customers using our online forms is kept strictly confidential and secure to prevent unauthorized use of personal information.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use the personal information you have provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

## QUESTIONNAIRES AND SURVEYS

On some occasions upon entering any one of the NextEra Energy Sites you may be asked to complete either an online survey or questionnaire. These surveys and questionnaires will deal with your opinions, attitudes, interests, and more generally about your activities online. It is important that you answer these surveys and questionnaires accurately for they represent our only means to improve our services offered through our websites. Any personal information gathered from your participation in questionnaires or surveys through any one of our sites will not be kept unless you agree to provide us with that information.

## REVIEW OF AND CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may review the personal information you have provided to us by logging in to your account with us. Please note that your username and password will need to be provided in order to review your account information. Please also note that some account information, including without limitation the service address and the account user id, may not be changed.

If you need to correct or update your personal information provided to us, please contact an account representative via telephone using the following telephone numbers:

For residential customers, you may use the following telephone numbers:

Boca/Delray: 561-994-8227  
Bradenton: 941-917-0708  
Broward: 954-797-5000  
Cocoa: 321-723-7795  
Dade: 305-442-8770  
Daytona: 386-252-1541  
Ft. Myers: 239-334-7754  
Ft. Pierce: 772-462-0555  
Jupiter: 561-697-8000  
Melbourne: 321-723-7795  
Naples: 239-262-1322  
Punta Gorda: 941-639-1106  
Sarasota: 941-917-0708  
Stuart: 772-287-5400  
West Palm Beach: 561-697-8000  
Other Areas: 800-226-3545

Business customers may use the following telephone numbers:

Broward: 954-581-5668  
Dade: 305-442-0388  
West Palm Beach: 561-478-6399  
All other areas: 800-375-2434

In addition, certain information may be updated by completing the form on the reverse side of your monthly service invoice and returning the form in the envelope supplied with your monthly service invoice.

## BROWSER SETTINGS

For more information on Internet browser settings affecting our security features, visit _[Recommended Browser Settings.](http://www.fpl.com/faqs/content/website_tech/browsers.shtml)_

## SENDING NEXTERA ENERGY ADVERTISEMENTS

We may send out periodic emails informing customers of offers related to a service they requested. Customers will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential service.

While visitors of our sites cannot send any of our posted advertisements via email, visitors can request that we send ads on their behalf. Before we can satisfy any requests, visitors must provide their name and the third party's email address. This information is used to send the specified advertisement.

Customers who do not wish to receive NextEra Energy promotional emails on new products and services may _[click here to notify us](http://app.fpl.com/sowww2/SowwwHtmlController?command=emailPrefUpdate)_.

## CHILDREN MAY NOT USE THE NEXTERA ENERGY SITES

The NextEra Energy Sites are intended to be used by adults only, and not directed towards children under the age of eighteen. If you are under eighteen, you are not eligible to use the NextEra Energy Sites. If you believe that we have collected personal information from children under the age of eighteen, please notify us immediately so that we may take steps to eliminate such information.

## A WARNING ABOUT E-MAIL THAT WE SEND; A WARNING ABOUT “PHISHING”

We may send you emails from time to time to provide you with energy-saving ideas and other useful information, updates regarding our services, and special offers (whether available directly from NextEra Energy or from one or more of our business partners). Likewise, we may from time to time call the phone number associated with your account.

However, we do not and will not at any time request any of the following information via email or through any telephone call initiated by NextEra Energy:

  * your account user ID

  * your account password

  * your social security number

  * your credit card and/or bank information

Likewise, we will never send you an unsolicited email containing a link to the log in page for our website.

If you receive an email or telephone call requesting any of this information, it is likely that you have received an attempted theft of your identity commonly called “phishing.” Likewise, if you receive an email urging you to login to your account and provides you with a link to the login page, it is also likely that you have received a “phishing” attempt. In either case, you should bring the email to the attention of our security department by forwarding the email to: _[http://www.fpl.com/contact](http://www.fpl.com/contact/index.shtml)_

If we send you an email requesting that you login to your account, we strongly recommend that you open your web browser and manually input the address for our website. Doing so will ensure that you do not open some third-party website disguised to look like our website.

For more information about “phishing,” you should visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at _[www.ftc.gov.](http://www.ftc.gov/)_

## WARNING ABOUT SOCIAL MEDIA

In order to provide both current and potential customers with more options for contacting Florida Power & Light Company’s Customer Service department (“FPL”), FPL has established Facebook and Twitter accounts. As these are public forums, you should be aware that any personal information you choose to disclose through those platforms can be read, collected or used by others and that such disclosures are subject solely to the Privacy Policies and protections of those forums. FPL has no control over those forums and, thus, is not responsible for any personal information you may choose to disclose through them. You should also be aware that FPL will never disclose, or ask for you to disclose, your non-public, personally identifying information (such as your Social Security number, bank information, etc.) through these public forums. FPL recommends that you not submit your non-public, personally identifying information through these avenues. If there is a need for such information, FPL will provide you alternative communication methods.

## EFFECTIVE DATE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**_This Privacy Policy is effective May 25, 2010._**

We reserve the right to alter or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you in order to reflect changes in our online information practices. In an effort to ensure that you receive notice of any changes to the Privacy Policy, we may include a notice on our website. Alternatively, we may send a notice to the email address you provide to us; however, if you do not provide us with an email address, we will not be able to provide you with such notice.

We also recommend that you check back with this web page periodically so that you may be kept informed regarding any changes to the Privacy Policy. You should also visit our _[Terms of Use](http://www.fplgroup.com/contents/legal_notice.shtml)_ in addition to this Privacy Policy each time you visit any one of the NextEra Energy Sites.

## THIRD PARTY LINKS

The NextEra Energy Sites may contain links to third party websites that are not subject to the Privacy Policy. If you visit these websites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies before providing them with any personal information.

## STATE LAW

You may have privacy rights under applicable state law in addition to those outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## CONTACT US

If you choose to email us through the “Contact Us” link on this site, you will be asked to provide information such as your name and email address so that one our employees can respond to your questions and comments. If however, you wish to submit your questions or comments via U.S. mail they can be mailed to:

Attn: Customer Care  
700 Universe Blvd.  
Juno Beach, Florida 33408
